A Guide to the Governor J. Lindsay Almond, Jr., Executive records, 1958-1962
Library of Virginia
- Series II: General Correspondence, 1958-1962., Extent: 38 cu. ft. [75 boxes]. (Box 79-153)
  - American Heritage Foundation (Box 79)
  - American Legion (Box 79)
  - American Red Cross (Box 79)
  - Appointments (With Governor), 1958-1959 (Box 79)
  - Appointments (With Governor), 1959-1961 (Box 80)
  - Astronaut (Box 81)
  - Automobile Club of Virginia (Box 81)
  - Barradas's Law (Box 81)
  - "Belona Arsenal," Purchase of (Box 81)
  - Benjamin Franklin 250th Anniversary (Box 81)
  - Bill of Rights (Box 81)
  - Blue Cross Blue Shield (Box 81)
  - Booker T. Washington Birthplace Memorial (Box 81)
  - Boy Scouts of America (Box 81)
  - Brussels World Fair (Box 81)
  - Cape Henry Day (Box 82)
  - Care (Box 82)
  - Chamber of Commerce, Junior (Box 82)
  - Chamber of Commerce, Richmond (Box 82)
  - Chamber of Commerce, United States (Box 82)
  - Chamber of Commerce, Virginia, 1958-1961 (Box 82)
  - Chantilly Airport (Box 82)
  - Citizenship (Box 82)
  - Civil Rights (Box 83)
  - Colonial Williamsburg (Box 83)
  - Commissions Issued, 1958-1961 (Box 83)
  - Communism (Box 83)
  - Community Fund (Box 84)
  - Confederate Memorial Literary Society (Box 84)
  - Constitution of the United States (Box 84)
  - Council of State Governments, 1958-1959 (Box 84)
  - Council of State Governments, 1959-1960 (Box 85)
  - Council of State Governments, 1960-1961 (Box 86)
  - Council of State Governments, 1961 (Box 87)
  - Counties (Box 87)
  - Daylight Savings Time (Box 87)
  - Deeds (Box 87)
  - Defenders of State Sovereignty and Individual Liberties (Box 87)
  - Delegates Designated by Governor, 1958-1961 (Box 88)
  - Democratic Campaign (Box 89)
  - National Democratic Committee, 1958-1959 (Box 89)
  - National Democratic Committee, 1960-1961 (Box 90)
  - National Democratic Convention (Box 90-91)
  - Democratic State Central Committee (Box 92)
  - Department Heads (Box 92)
  - Depressed area, Dickinson County (Box 92)
  - Dismal Swamp Industrial Canal (Box 92)
  - Drivers permits (Box 92)
  - Drunk drivers (Box 92)
  - Elections (Box 92)
  - Emancipation Day (Box 92)
  - Escheator (Box 92)
  - Extradition matters (Box 92)
  - Executive orders (Box 92)
  - Federal Boating Act (Box 92)
  - Federal Bureau of Investigation (Box 93)
  - Federal Electoral College (Box 93)
  - Federal Legislation, 1959-1959 (Box 93)
  - Federal Legislation, 1960-1961 (Box 94)
  - Federal Mine Safety (Box 95)
  - Federal Minimum Wage Proposal (Box 95)
  - Federal Port of New York (Box 95)
  - Federation of Women's Clubs (Box 95)
  - Flags, 1959-1962 (Box 95)
  - Floods (Box 95)
  - Fluoridation (Box 95)
  - Foreign correspondence (Box 95)
  - Freedom Forest (Box 95)
  - Garden Club of Virginia (Box 95)
  - General Assembly, 1958 (Box 96)
  - General Assembly, 1959-1962 (Box 97)
  - General Assembly, Barber Bill Literature (Box 98)
  - General Assembly, Commission to Study Laws Relating to Fish, Oysters, and Seafood (Box 98)
  - General Assembly, Commission to Study State Government (Box 98)
  - General Assembly, Digests of Acts of 1960 (Box 98)
  - General Assembly, Extra Session, 1958 (Box 98)
  - General Assembly, For Governor's Program, Sales Tax, Etc., 1960 (Box 98)
  - General Assembly, Gasoline Tax (Box 99)
  - General Assembly, Governor's Address to General Assembly (Box 99)
  - General Assembly, Hand guns (Box 99)
  - General Assembly, House, 1960 Session (Box 99)
  - General Assembly, House, 1958-1962 (Box 99)
  - General Assembly, House, Delegates, George Rich (Box 99)
  - General Assembly, House, Bill No. 28 (Box 99)
  - General Assembly, House, Bill No. 53, Tobacco Tax Veto (Box 99)
  - General Assembly, House, Bill No. 111 (Box 99)
  - General Assembly, House, Bill No. 279, Blue Laws (Box 99)
  - General Assembly, House, Bill No. 373, Boating (Box 99)
  - General Assembly, House, Bill No. 394 (Box 100)
  - General Assembly, House, Bill No. 444 (Box 100)
  - General Assembly, House, Bill No. 444, Veto (Box 100)
  - General Assembly, House, Bill No. 647, Veterinary (Box 100)
  - General Assembly, House, Bill No. 723, Pupil Placement (Box 100)
  - General Assembly, House, Notes on Bills, 1958-1960 (Box 101)
  - General Assembly, Legislature, Advisory Committee on Physical Therapy (Box 101)
  - General Assembly, Legislature, Advisory Council on Nurse Training (Box 101)
  - General Assembly, Legislature, Agricultural Research and Education Commission (Box 101)
  - General Assembly, Legislature, Study Commissions, Children Born Out of Wedlock (Box 101)
  - General Assembly, Legislature, Study Commissions, Industrial Loan Association (Box 101)
  - General Assembly, Legislature, Study Commissions, Juvenile Offenders (Box 101)
  - General Assembly, Messages, 1960 (Box 101)
  - General Assembly, Virginia-West Virginia Boundary Commission (Box 101)
  - General Assembly, Members of House, 1959-1961 (Box 102)
  - General Assembly, Interposition (Box 102)
  - General Assembly, Model, YMCA, 1958-1961 (Box 102)
  - General Assembly, Protest Governor's Program (Box 102)
  - General Assembly, Request William and Mary (Box 102)
  - General Assembly, Resolutions (Box 102)
  - General Assembly, Sale of whiskey by the drink, 1960-1962 (Box 102)
  - General Assembly, Sales Tax, 1958-1959 (Box 103)
  - General Assembly, Sales Tax, Information, 1959 (Box 103)
  - General Assembly, Sales Tax, Suggestions, 1959 (Box 103)
  - General Assembly, Sales Tax, Protests, Tobacco and All Taxes, 1960 (Box 103)
  - General Assembly, Sales Tax, Suggestions, 1960 (Box 103)
  - General Assembly, School textbooks, 1958 (Box 103)
  - General Assembly, Senate, 1960 session (Box 103)
  - General Assembly, Senate, 1958-1962 (Box 103)
  - General Assembly, Senate Bill No. 119 (Box 103)
  - General Assembly, Senate Bill No. 294 (Box 104)
  - General Assembly, Senate Bill No. 310 (Box 104)
  - General Assembly, Senate, Extra Session, 1959 (Box 104)
  - General Assembly, Senate, Members, 1959-19561 (Box 104)
  - General Assembly, Senate, Notes on Bills, 1958-1960 (Box 104)
  - General Assembly, Senate, Special Session, 1959 (Box 104)
  - General Assembly, Senate, Special Session, 1959, Bills Signed by Governor (Box 104)
  - General Assembly, Senate, Special Session, 1959, House (Box 105)
  - General Assembly, Senate, Special Session, 1959, Request for and Suggestions (Box 105)
  - General Assembly, Senate, Special Session, 1959, Senate (Box 105)
  - General Assembly, Studies (Box 105)
  - General Assembly, Teacher's Salaries (Box 105)
  - General Assembly, "The 3 Day Week End" (Box 105)
  - General Assembly, Trailers (Box 105)
  - General Assembly, Trespass Law (Box 105)
  - General Assembly, Whitehead (Box 105)
  - General Assembly, Williamsburg, Session, 1960 (Box 105)
  - Governor's Conference, 1958 January-May (Box 105)
  - Governor's Conference, 1958 June-December (Box 106)
  - Governor's Conference, 1959 (Box 106)
  - Governor's Conference, 1959, Thank You's (Box 107)
  - Governor's Conference, 1960, List of Governors (Box 107)
  - Governor's Conference, 1960, Gifts (Box 107)
  - Governor's Conference, 1960, Mo Winfree (Box 107)
  - Governor's Conference, 1961, and Honolulu (Box 108)
  - Governor's Conference, 1961, Gifts and Calls (Box 108)
  - Governor's Conference, 1961, Reports (Box 108)
  - Governor's Conference, 1961, Resolutions (Box 108)
  - Governors of other states, 1958 (Box 108)
  - Governors of other states, 1959-1960 (Box 109)
  - Governors of other states, 1960-1961 (Box 110)
  - Governors of other states, 1961 (Box 111)
  - Governor's South American Trip (Box 111)
  - Governor's Wives, Salaries, Assistant, Retirement, and Flower (Box 111)
  - Girl Scouts (Box 111)
  - Gunston Hall, Board of Regents (Box 111)
  - Hall of Fame (Box 111)
  - Hampton Roads Maritime Association, Inc. (Box 111)
  - Hobby (Box 111)
  - Holiday information (Box 111)
  - Home for Confederate Women (Box 111)
  - Horse racing (Box 111)
  - Hurricane (Box 111)
  - Inaugural Address and Ceremonies (Box 111)
  - Inauguration (Box 111)
  - Indians (Box 111)
  - Inflation (Box 111)
  - Information, Virginia Misc. (Box 111)
  - Intergovernmental Relations Commission (Box 112)
  - Izaak Walton League (Box 112)
  - Invitations, 1960 January-March (Box 112)
  - Invitations, 1960 April-July (Box 113)
  - Invitations, 1960 August-November (Box 114)
  - Invitations, 1960 November-December (Box 115)
  - Invitations, 1961 January-April (Box 115)
  - Invitations, 1961 May-September (Box 116)
  - Invitations, 1961 October-December (Box 117)
  - Invitations, 1962 (Box 117)
  - Invitations, Extended, 1958-1959 (Box 117)
  - Invitations, Extended, 1960-1962 (Box 117)
  - Invitations, Time Indefinite (Box 117)
  - Jamestown Foundation, Board of Trustees (Box 117)
  - Judicial Council (Box 118)
  - Juvenile Delinquency (Box 118)
  - Keep Virginia Beautiful (Box 118)
  - Krushchev, Visit (Box 118)
  - Labor, Labor Unions, 1961 (Box 118)
  - Law Enforcement (Box 118)
  - League of Municipalities (Box 118)
  - Robert E. Lee Memorial Foundation (Box 118)
  - Legal matters, 1958 (Box 118)
  - Legal matters, 1959-1962 (Box 119)
  - Legislation (Box 119)
  - Letters of Commendation, 1958-1962 (Box 119)
  - Letters of Compliments (Box 119)
  - Letters of Congratulations, 1958, Bellamy Award (Box 119)
  - Letters of Congratulations, 1959 (Box 119)
  - Letters of Congratulations, 1960, Helen Keller Award (Box 119)
  - Letters of Congratulations, 1961 (Box 119)
  - Letters, Good Wishes, 1958-1959 (Box 120)
  - Letters, Welcome, 1960-1961 (Box 120)
  - Letters of Introduction (Box 120)
  - Letters of Recommendation (Box 120)
  - Letters returned, 1960-1962 (Box 120)
  - Letters to Heads of Departments (Box 120)
  - Lincoln Sesquicentennial Commission (Box 120)
  - Litterbug (Box 120)
  - Local affairs (Box 121)
  - MacArthur Memorial in Norfolk (Box 121)
  - March of Dimes (Box 121)
  - Mariners Museum (Box 121)
  - Metropolitan Area, Compact, National Capital Transportation Agency (Box 121)
  - Metropolitan Area, Water problem (Box 121)
  - Washington Metropolitan Regional Conference (Box 122)
  - Miller School of Albemarle, Board of Trustees (Box 122)
  - Mount Vernon, Board of Visitors, 1958-1962 (Box 122)
  - Mount Vernon, Sewage Disposal (Box 122)
  - Music (Box 122)
  - National Educational Association (Box 122)
  - National Employment of Physically Handicapped, 1958-1961 (Box 123)
  - National Freedom Day (Box 123)
  - National Kidney Disease Foundation (Box 123)
  - National Rivers and Harbors Congress (Box 124)
  - National Safety Council (Box 124)
  - National Society Daughters of the American Revolution (Box 124)
  - Newman, Richard Berryman (Box 124)
  - Nixon, Richard (Box 124)
  - Notaries (Box 124)
  - Oddity, 1960-1961 (Box 124)
  - Oddity, Abell, Royal Allen, 1960-1961 (Box 125)
  - Patrick Henry Boys Plantation (Box 125)
  - Photographs (Box 125)
  - Pocahontas (Box 125)
  - Politics, 1958-1960 (Box 125)
  - Politics, 1960-1961 (Box 126)
  - Politics, Third Party (Box 126)
  - Portrait (Box 126)
  - Powers, Pilot U-2 (Box 126)
  - Press, 1958-1962 (Box 126)
  - Press, Newspaper (Box 126)
  - Proclamations, 1958 (Box 126)
  - Proclamations, 1959 (Box 127)
  - Proclamation data, A-Z, 1960-1961 (Box 127)
  - Queen Elizabeth (Box 127)
  - Racial (Box 128)
  - Bi-Racial Commission (Box 128)
  - Radio Broadcasts, 1958-1960 (Box 128)
  - Radio Broadcasts, 1961-1962 (Box 128)
  - Radio Stations, W.R.N.L. (Box 129)
  - Radio Stations, W.R.V.A. (Box 129)
  - Recipes (Box 129)
  - Reciprocity Board (Box 129)
  - Rent problems (Box 129)
  - Requests, 1959 January-May (Box 129)
  - Requests, 1959 June-December (Box 130)
  - Requests, 1960 January-April (Box 130)
  - Requests, 1960 May-December (Box 131)
  - Requests, 1961 January-June (Box 132)
  - Requests, 1961 July-December (Box 133)
  - Requests, Flags (Box 133)
  - Requests, For Pony, Foreign (Box 133)
  - Requests, Raise in Salary (Box 133)
  - Resolutions (Box 134)
  - Resources for the Future, Inc. (Box 134)
  - Rewards, Jackson case (Box 134)
  - Rewards, Lindsay case (Box 134)
  - Richmond, City of (Box 134)
  - Right to Work (Box 134)
  - Safety, 1958-1959 (Box 134)
  - Safety, 1960-1962 (Box 135)
  - Safety, Seat belts (Box 135)
  - Salvation Army (Box 135)
  - Segregation, 1960-1961 (Box 135)
  - Segregation, Churches, 1958 (Box 135)
  - Segregation, Claim for School Funds (Box 135)
  - Segregation, Closing of Schools (Box 135)
  - Segregation, Closing White and Colored Schools (Box 135)
  - Segregation, Federal Opinions, U.S. Supreme Court (Box 135)
  - Segregation, Frank, Rabbi Emmett A. (Box 135)
  - Segregation, Governor's Stand, 1958 (Box 135)
  - Segregation, Integration, 1959-1961 (Box 165)
  - Segregation, "Let My People Go" (Box 136)
  - Segregation, Litigation (Box 136)
  - Segregation, Little Rock, 1958-1959 (Box 136)
  - Segregation, N.A.A.C.P., 1958-1959 (Box 136)
  - Segregation, N.A.A.C.P., undated (Box 136)
  - Segregation, Norfolk, 1958 (Box 136)
  - Segregation, Petitions, 1959 (Box 136)
  - Segregation, Public schools (Box 137)
  - Segregation, Re-opening schools (Box 137)
  - Segregation, Resolutions (Box 137)
  - Segregation, Teachers (Box 137)
  - Segregation, Virginia Education Fund (Box 137)
  - Segregation, Withdrawals (Box 137)
  - Social Security (Box 138)
  - Sons of the American Revolution (Box 138)
  - Southern Governor's Conference, 1958-1959 (Box 138)
  - Southern Governor's Conference, 1959, Mrs. Evans file (Box 138)
  - Southern Governor's Conference, 1960 (Box 138)
  - Southern Governor's Conference, 1961 (Box 139)
  - Southern Governor's Conference, "Appalachian Governors" (Box 139)
  - Southern Governor's Conference, Appalachian Governors, The White House (Box 139)
  - Southern Governor's Conference, Foreign imports, 1959-1960 (Box 139)
  - Southern Governor's Conference, Gifts, 1959-1960 (Box 140)
  - Southern Regional Education Board, 1959 (Box 140)
  - Southern Regional Education Board, 1960-1961 (Box 141)
  - Southern Regional Education Board, Atomic Energy Compact, 1958-1961 (Box 142)
  - Southern Regional Education Board, Magnuson Bill (Box 142)
  - Southern States Industrial Council (Box 142)
  - Speech materials, Information (Box 143)
  - Speeches by Governor, A-C (Box 143)
  - Speeches by Governor, D-G (Box 144)
  - Speeches by Governor, H-I (Box 144)
  - Speeches by Governor, J-M (Box 144)
  - Speeches by Governor, N-S (Box 145)
  - Speeches by Governor, T-Z (Box 145)
  - Speeches by Governor, Constitution (Box 145)
  - Speeches by Governor, Constitution Amendment (Box 145)
  - Statements, 1958 January-March (Box 145)
  - Statements, 1958 April-June (Box 146)
  - Statements, 1958 July-December (Box 146)
  - Statements, 1959 January-March (Box 146)
  - Statements, 1959 April-June (Box 146)
  - Statements, 1959 July-December (Box 146)
  - Statements, 1960, A-C (Box 146)
  - Statements, 1960, D-J (Box 147)
  - Statements, 1960, L-R (Box 147)
  - Statements, 1960, S-Y (Box 147)
  - Statements, 1961, A-E (Box 147)
  - Statements, 1961, F-P (Box 147)
  - Statements, 1961, Q-Y (Box 148)
  - States Rights, Virginia (Box 148)
  - Stonewall Jackson Memorial, Inc. (Box 148)
  - Strikes (Box 148)
  - Surplus Property (Box 148)
  - Taxes, Misc., 1958-1960 (Box 148)
  - Taxes, Misc., 1961 (Box 149)
  - Taxes, Sales Tax Information, 1960 (Box 149)
  - Telecasting (Box 149)
  - Television (Box 149)
  - Thanksgiving (Box 149)
  - Theodore Roosevelt Centennial Commission (Box 149)
  - Thomas Jefferson Memorial Foundation (Box 149)
  - Tickets (Box 150)
  - Tobacco Bowl Festival (Box 150)
  - Tolbert, Dr. William Richard Jr. (Box 150)
  - Traffic, Court Conference in Virginia (Box 150)
  - Traffic, Violations, 1958-1959 (Box 150)
  - Traffic, Violations, 1960-1961 (Box 151)
  - Treaties (Box 151)
  - Trucker's Boycott (Box 151)
  - Tuberculosis (Box 151)
  - Tunney, Gene (Box 151)
  - Tusing, J.M. (Box 151)
  - United Daughters of the Confederacy (Box 151)
  - United Fund of Virginia (Box 151)
  - United Nations Organization (Box 151)
  - Veterans Administration (Box 151)
  - Veterans Affairs (Box 152)
  - Veterans Bonus (Box 152)
  - Veterans Disabled American (Box 152)
  - Veterans Foreign Wars (Box 152)
  - Virginia Citizens Strategy Panel (Box 152)
  - Virginia Congress of Parents and Teachers (Box 152)
  - Virginia Education Association (Box 152)
  - Virginia Farm Bureau Federation (Box 152)
  - Virginia Federation of Garden Clubs (Box 152)
  - Virginia Foundation for Independent Colleges (Box 152)
  - Virginia Highway Users Association (Box 152)
  - Virginia Inter-Agency Committee on Recreation (Box 153)
  - Virginia State Poultry Federation (Box 153)
  - Virginia State Rifle and Revolver Association, Inc. (Box 153)
  - Virginia Travel Council (Box 153)
  - Virginia Womens Club (Box 153)
  - Voting, Residency requirements (Box 153)
  - Wall, Barrye (Box 153)
  - War Memorial Museum of Virginia (Box 153)
  - Washington, George (Box 153)
  - Woodrow Wilson National Fellowship Foundation (Box 153)
  - World's Fair (Box 153)
  - World Peace (Box 153)
  - World War II (Box 153)
  - Young Democrats of Virginia (Box 153)
- Series III: Federal Government, 1958-1962., Extent: 8 cu. ft. [16 boxes]. (Box 154-169)
  The Federal Government records are housed in 16 boxes and are arranged alphabetically by agency or subject. Subjects include: Army, Civil War Centennial Commission, Defense, and Executive Departments.
  - United States, Misc., Archives (Box 154)
  - United States, Misc., Blue RIdge Parkway Association (Box 154)
  - United States, Misc., Central Intelligence Agency (Box 154)
  - United States, Misc., Education, Federal Aid (Box 154)
  - United States, Misc., Marshall (Box 154)
  - United States, Misc., National Science Foundation (Box 154)
  - United States, Misc., Peace Corps (Box 154)
  - United States, Misc., Secretary of Defense (Box 154)
  - United States, Misc., Youth Conservation Corps (Box 154)
  - Armed Forces, Air Corps (Box 154)
  - Armed Forces, Army (Box 154)
  - Armed Forces, Army, Discharges (Box 155)
  - Armed Forces, Army, Draft Board (Box 155)
  - Armed Forces, Army, Hardship (Box 155)
  - Armed Forces, Army, Engineer District Corps of Engineers, 1958 (Box 155)
  - Armed Forces, Army, Engineer District Corps of Engineers, 1959-1960 (Box 155)
  - Armed Forces, Army, Engineer District Corps of Engineers, 1961 January-June (Box 155)
  - Armed Forces, Army, Engineer District Corps of Engineers, 1961 July-December (Box 155)
  - Armed Forces, Army, Engineer District Corps of Engineers, Salem Church Dam (Box 155)
  - Coast Guard (Box 156)
  - Commissions, Atomic Energy Commission, 1958-1959 (Box 156)
  - Commissions, Atomic Energy Commission, 1960-1961 (Box 157)
  - Commissions, On Civil Rights (Box 157)
  - Commissions, Civil War Centennial Commission, 1958 (Box 157)
  - Commissions, Civil War Centennial Commission, 1959 (Box 158)
  - Commissions, Civil War Centennial Commission, 1960 (Box 158)
  - Commissions, Civil War Centennial Commission, 1961 January-March (Box 158)
  - Commissions, Civil War Centennial Commission, 1961 April-June (Box 159)
  - Commissions, Civil War Centennial Commission, 1961 May 6, Salem Church (Box 159)
  - Commissions, Civil War Centennial Commission, 1961 July-December (Box 159)
  - Commissions, Civil War Centennial Commission, 1961 July 22-23, Governors invited (Box 159)
  - Commission, Federal Communications (Box 159)
  - Commissions, Federal Power (Box 160)
  - Commissions, Interstate Commerce (Box 160)
  - Commissions, James Monroe Foundation, 1958-1962 (Box 160)
  - Commissions, Maritime (Box 160)
  - Commissions, Make Plans and Arrangements for Centennial Celebration of Woodrow Wilson, 1950-1953 (Box 160)
  - Commissions, Make Plans and Arrangements for Centennial Celebration of Woodrow Wilson, 1954-1958 (Box 160)
  - Commissions, Make Plans and Arrangements for Centennial Celebration of Woodrow Wilson, 1959-1961 (Box 161)
  - Commission, To Provide Memorial to Chief Justice John Marshall (Box 161)
  - Congress and Senate (Box 161)
  - Defense, Civil Defense, 1958 January-June (Box 162)
  - Defense, Civil Defense, 1958 July-December (Box 162)
  - Defense, Civil Defense, 1959 (Box 162)
  - Defense, Civil Defense, 1960 (Box 162)
  - Defense, Civil Defense, 1961 (Box 163)
  - Defense, Selective Service, Undated (Box 163)
  - Defense, Selective Service, Recommendations, 1960 (Box 163)
  - Departments, Agriculture, 1958-1960 (Box 164)
  - Departments, Agriculture, 1961-1962 (Box 164)
  - Departments, Commerce, 1958-1960 (Box 164)
  - Departments, Commerce, 1961 (Box 164)
  - Departments, Health, Education, and Welfare, 1958-1959 (Box 165)
  - Departments, Health, Education, and Welfare, 1960 (Box 165)
  - Departments, Health, Education, and Welfare, 1961 (Box 165)
  - Departments, Interior, Undated (Box 165)
  - Departments, Interior, 1961-1962 (Box 166)
  - Departments, Justice, U.S. Attorney General, Bravery Medals (Box 166)
  - Departments, Justice, U.S. Attorney General, Undated (Box 166)
  - Departments, Labor (Box 166)
  - Departments, Labor, Undated (Box 166)
  - Departments, Navy, Naming Ship Williamsburg (Box 166)
  - Departments, State, Undated (Box 167)
  - Departments, State, U.S. Chief of Protocal regarding Hospitality for Diplomats (Box 167)
  - Departments, Extra copies letters regarding Foreign Diplomats (Box 167)
  - Departments, Treasury, Internal Revenue (Box 167)
  - Departments, Treasury, Post Office, Commission Stamps (Box 167)
  - Departments, Treasury, Savings Bonds (Box 167)
  - Government, President Eisenhower (Box 168)
  - Government, President Kennedy (Box 168)
  - Government, President, Recommendations (Box 168)
  - Government, Vice-President (Box 168)
  - Government, Pre-Inaugural Committee, 1961 (Box 168)
  - Government, President's Committee for Traffic Safety (Box 168)
  - Government, President's Council on Youth Fitness (Box 168)
  - Government, President's Foreign Aid Program (Box 168)
  - Government, White House Conference on Aging, 1961 (Box 169)
  - Government, White House Conference on Children and Youth, 1959-1960 (Box 169)
  - Government, White House Conference on Children and Youth, 1961 (Box 169)
  - Government, Merchant Marines (Box 169)
  - Government, Marines (Box 169)
- Series IV: Extraditions, 1958-1962., Extent: 4 cu. ft. [8 boxes]. (Box 170-178)
  The Extradition records are housed in 9 boxes and are arranged alphabetically.
  - A (Box 170)
  - Adey-Von Atzinger (Box 170)
  - B (Box 170)
  - Baer-Brittle (Box 170)
  - C (Box 170)
  - Cahill (Box 170)
  - Campbell-Crumpler (Box 171)
  - D (Box 171)
  - Daniels-Dosher (Box 171)
  - E (Box 171)
  - Eads-Ensmerger (Box 171)
  - F (Box 171)
  - Farmer-Fulton (Box 171)
  - G (Box 171)
  - Gillespie-Guinn (Box 172)
  - H (Box 172)
  - Haire-Hyatt (Box 172)
  - I (Box 172)
  - J (Box 172)
  - Jackson-Jordan (Box 173)
  - K (Box 173)
  - Karmasin-Kirwin (Box 173)
  - L (Box 173)
  - Lane-Lowinger (Box 173)
  - McM (Box 173)
  - McConnell-McWaters (Box 173)
  - M (Box 174)
  - Marconi-Murphy (Box 174)
  - N (Box 174)
  - Nassau-Neeley (Box 174)
  - O (Box 174)
  - Ogburn-O'Neill (Box 174)
  - P (Box 174)
  - Paramore-Pulliam (Box 175)
  - Q (Box 175)
  - R (Box 175)
  - Radford-Russ (Box 175)
  - S (Box 175)
  - Seabrook-Sparks (Box 175)
  - Stanley-Swiney (Box 176)
  - T (Box 176)
  - Taylor-Toler (Box 176)
  - U (Box 176)
  - V (Box 176)
  - Vaughan (Box 176)
  - W (Box 176)
  - Wade-Wheeler (Box 176)
  - Wheeling-Wright (Box 177)
  - X,Y,Z (Box 177)
  - Zinicola (Box 177)
  - Card file on pardons (Box 177)
  - Requisitions (Box 177)
  - Waivers, Signed by fugitives (Box 178)
- Series V: Judicial, 1958-1962., Extent: 3 cu. ft. [6 boxes]. (Box 179-184)
  The Judicial records are housed in 6 boxes and are arranged by Court.
  - Attorney General, 1958 (Box 179)
  - Attorney General, 1959 (Box 179)